{"uuid": "a10bfd10-bc3c-4c0d-91bb-d2fa3007bd00", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "C=CCc1c(C=O)c(C(C)CC)c(F)c(NC)c1OC(N)=O", "smiles_random": "c1(c(CC=C)c(C=O)c(C(CC)C)c(c1NC)F)OC(N)=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(c(CC=C)c(C=O)c(C(CC)C)c(c1NC)F)OC(N)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "C=CCc1c(C=O)c(C(C)CC)c(F)c(NC)c1OC(N)=O", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "c8a1a8c8-565d-49f1-86bb-31c8455f53de", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "C=CCc1c(OC)c(I)c(C(C)C)c(C#N)c1C1CCCCC1", "smiles_random": "C(C=C)c1c(OC)c(c(c(C#N)c1C1CCCCC1)C(C)C)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC(C=C)c1c(OC)c(c(c(C#N)c1C1CCCCC1)C(C)C)I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "C=CCc1c(OC)c(I)c(C(C)C)c(C#N)c1C1CCCCC1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "b618c527-5baf-4860-b1b2-e437fac71b0d", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "C#CCc1c(Br)c(C(C)C)c(NC(N)=O)c(CC=C)c1S(N)(=O)=O", "smiles_random": "C(C)(C)c1c(c(c(S(=O)(N)=O)c(c1Br)CC#C)CC=C)NC(=O)N"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC(C)(C)c1c(c(c(S(=O)(N)=O)c(c1Br)CC#C)CC=C)NC(=O)N\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "C#CCc1c(Br)c(C(C)C)c(NC(N)=O)c(CC=C)c1S(N)(=O)=O", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "2241b995-168e-4180-9d5c-88b5161941b3", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCCc1c(S(N)(=O)=O)c(NC(N)=O)c(C#N)c(C2CCCCC2)c1S(=O)(=O)O", "smiles_random": "O=C(N)Nc1c(S(N)(=O)=O)c(c(c(C2CCCCC2)c1C#N)S(=O)(=O)O)CCC"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nO=C(N)Nc1c(S(N)(=O)=O)c(c(c(C2CCCCC2)c1C#N)S(=O)(=O)O)CCC\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCCc1c(S(N)(=O)=O)c(NC(N)=O)c(C#N)c(C2CCCCC2)c1S(=O)(=O)O", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "04a96072-0927-4cb2-a565-144c4029fb06", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCc1c(C(=O)OC(C)=O)c(Cl)c(NC(N)=O)c(-c2ccccc2)c1C(C)C", "smiles_random": "O=C(OC(=O)C)c1c(CC)c(c(c(c1Cl)NC(=O)N)-c1ccccc1)C(C)C"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nO=C(OC(=O)C)c1c(CC)c(c(c(c1Cl)NC(=O)N)-c1ccccc1)C(C)C\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCc1c(C(=O)OC(C)=O)c(Cl)c(NC(N)=O)c(-c2ccccc2)c1C(C)C", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "1716a9a1-112a-4b18-853b-e5676c1c51ec", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCC(C)c1c(SC)c(C(=O)O)c(C#N)c(Br)c1C(=O)OC", "smiles_random": "OC(c1c(c(Br)c(C(=O)OC)c(C(CC)C)c1SC)C#N)=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nOC(c1c(c(Br)c(C(=O)OC)c(C(CC)C)c1SC)C#N)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCC(C)c1c(SC)c(C(=O)O)c(C#N)c(Br)c1C(=O)OC", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "65ec660d-1c02-4c89-a3b6-b4267cf0dba4", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "C#CCc1c(CCCC)c(Br)c(N)c(C=O)c1NC", "smiles_random": "c1(c(c(NC)c(CC#C)c(CCCC)c1Br)C=O)N"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(c(c(NC)c(CC#C)c(CCCC)c1Br)C=O)N\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "C#CCc1c(CCCC)c(Br)c(N)c(C=O)c1NC", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "318a58c8-0623-4a28-be87-542bd027d343", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "C#Cc1c(NC(C)=O)c(Cl)c(C(C)CC)c(S(N)(=O)=O)c1-c1ccccc1", "smiles_random": "NS(=O)(=O)c1c(-c2ccccc2)c(c(NC(=O)C)c(Cl)c1C(CC)C)C#C"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nNS(=O)(=O)c1c(-c2ccccc2)c(c(NC(=O)C)c(Cl)c1C(CC)C)C#C\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "C#Cc1c(NC(C)=O)c(Cl)c(C(C)CC)c(S(N)(=O)=O)c1-c1ccccc1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "21e95f50-b933-40c2-afde-e65018b6cd08", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CC(=O)Nc1c(C=O)c(N(C)C)c(S(=O)(=O)O)c(C(F)(F)F)c1OC(N)=O", "smiles_random": "C(=O)c1c(N(C)C)c(S(=O)(O)=O)c(c(OC(=O)N)c1NC(=O)C)C(F)(F)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC(=O)c1c(N(C)C)c(S(=O)(O)=O)c(c(OC(=O)N)c1NC(=O)C)C(F)(F)F\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CC(=O)Nc1c(C=O)c(N(C)C)c(S(=O)(=O)O)c(C(F)(F)F)c1OC(N)=O", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "5b68d89c-7c8c-4195-b83f-fd61bdbfcf17", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "C=CCc1c(C(C)=O)c(Br)c(C(=O)NC)c(CC)c1S(N)(=O)=O", "smiles_random": "C(Cc1c(c(c(c(Br)c1C(=O)C)C(NC)=O)CC)S(=O)(N)=O)=C"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC(Cc1c(c(c(c(Br)c1C(=O)C)C(NC)=O)CC)S(=O)(N)=O)=C\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "C=CCc1c(C(C)=O)c(Br)c(C(=O)NC)c(CC)c1S(N)(=O)=O", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "05b7ab76-e45e-4723-892b-77d91b131aea", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "C#CCc1c(C(=O)O)c(C(C)CC)c(SC)c(C2CCCCC2)c1C(=O)NC", "smiles_random": "S(C)c1c(C2CCCCC2)c(C(=O)NC)c(c(C(=O)O)c1C(C)CC)CC#C"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nS(C)c1c(C2CCCCC2)c(C(=O)NC)c(c(C(=O)O)c1C(C)CC)CC#C\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "C#CCc1c(C(=O)O)c(C(C)CC)c(SC)c(C2CCCCC2)c1C(=O)NC", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "a6905d5c-a518-4571-8425-1a6f7fac3c5d", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "C#Cc1c(F)c(C=C)c(C#N)c(CC=C)c1Br", "smiles_random": "c1(C=C)c(F)c(C#C)c(c(c1C#N)CC=C)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(C=C)c(F)c(C#C)c(c(c1C#N)CC=C)Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "C#Cc1c(F)c(C=C)c(C#N)c(CC=C)c1Br", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "19a941df-1eaa-462e-8eaf-3c055800ede0", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "C#CCc1c(NC(N)=O)c(C(=O)NC)c(CCCC)c(N(C)C)c1C(=O)OC(C)=O", "smiles_random": "C(=O)(C)OC(c1c(c(c(c(CCCC)c1N(C)C)C(=O)NC)NC(=O)N)CC#C)=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC(=O)(C)OC(c1c(c(c(c(CCCC)c1N(C)C)C(=O)NC)NC(=O)N)CC#C)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "C#CCc1c(NC(N)=O)c(C(=O)NC)c(CCCC)c(N(C)C)c1C(=O)OC(C)=O", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "15e9ac70-c714-4565-af87-5b6b66530001", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCCc1c(C)c(C(C)(C)C)c(NC)c(C2CC2)c1S(N)(=O)=O", "smiles_random": "O=S(N)(c1c(c(NC)c(C(C)(C)C)c(C)c1CCC)C1CC1)=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nO=S(N)(c1c(c(NC)c(C(C)(C)C)c(C)c1CCC)C1CC1)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCCc1c(C)c(C(C)(C)C)c(NC)c(C2CC2)c1S(N)(=O)=O", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "8e56ca41-94f3-40bb-bbb3-41a19e824d4b", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "NC(=O)Nc1c(F)c(Cl)c(S)c(S(=O)(=O)O)c1[N+](=O)[O-]", "smiles_random": "O=S(O)(=O)c1c(c(Cl)c(c(NC(N)=O)c1[N+](=O)[O-])F)S"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nO=S(O)(=O)c1c(c(Cl)c(c(NC(N)=O)c1[N+](=O)[O-])F)S\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "NC(=O)Nc1c(F)c(Cl)c(S)c(S(=O)(=O)O)c1[N+](=O)[O-]", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "06827be7-28e5-4aae-aeb5-69dbf37558e6", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCCCc1c(NC(N)=O)c(NC)c(F)c([N+](=O)[O-])c1C(C)CC", "smiles_random": "CCCCc1c(NC(=O)N)c(c(F)c([N+]([O-])=O)c1C(CC)C)NC"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nCCCCc1c(NC(=O)N)c(c(F)c([N+]([O-])=O)c1C(CC)C)NC\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCCCc1c(NC(N)=O)c(NC)c(F)c([N+](=O)[O-])c1C(C)CC", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "9cd93f7e-9f04-4498-adfa-229823de1b68", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CC(C)(C)c1c(Cl)c(C(=O)O)c(-c2ccccc2)c(C(F)(F)F)c1C#N", "smiles_random": "c1ccccc1-c1c(c(c(C(C)(C)C)c(Cl)c1C(O)=O)C#N)C(F)(F)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1ccccc1-c1c(c(c(C(C)(C)C)c(Cl)c1C(O)=O)C#N)C(F)(F)F\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CC(C)(C)c1c(Cl)c(C(=O)O)c(-c2ccccc2)c(C(F)(F)F)c1C#N", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "0a37784c-8e16-403a-9663-60545ed273ca", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "C#Cc1c(CC(C)C)c(NC(N)=O)c(C(=O)OC(C)=O)c(C)c1C(C)=O", "smiles_random": "O=C(Nc1c(CC(C)C)c(c(C(C)=O)c(c1C(=O)OC(C)=O)C)C#C)N"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nO=C(Nc1c(CC(C)C)c(c(C(C)=O)c(c1C(=O)OC(C)=O)C)C#C)N\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "C#Cc1c(CC(C)C)c(NC(N)=O)c(C(=O)OC(C)=O)c(C)c1C(C)=O", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "39eafd53-e681-49d4-bf0c-9e3b8ac720e5", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "C#Cc1c(C2CCCCC2)c(N)c(Br)c(S(=O)(=O)O)c1C(F)(F)F", "smiles_random": "Brc1c(c(C2CCCCC2)c(c(c1S(O)(=O)=O)C(F)(F)F)C#C)N"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nBrc1c(c(C2CCCCC2)c(c(c1S(O)(=O)=O)C(F)(F)F)C#C)N\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "C#Cc1c(C2CCCCC2)c(N)c(Br)c(S(=O)(=O)O)c1C(F)(F)F", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "a66118d0-e85e-4332-9673-bfe8b69a8539", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CNc1c(S)c(C=O)c(Br)c(C2CCCCC2)c1C(=O)O", "smiles_random": "C1CCCC(c2c(c(C=O)c(c(c2C(O)=O)NC)S)Br)C1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC1CCCC(c2c(c(C=O)c(c(c2C(O)=O)NC)S)Br)C1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CNc1c(S)c(C=O)c(Br)c(C2CCCCC2)c1C(=O)O", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "e92c6e96-00e3-4097-b4dc-e3dfa9f9fe9b", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCCc1c(Cl)c(C(=O)NC)c([N+](=O)[O-])c(I)c1OC(N)=O", "smiles_random": "c1(Cl)c(c(c(c(c1CCC)OC(N)=O)I)[N+]([O-])=O)C(NC)=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(Cl)c(c(c(c(c1CCC)OC(N)=O)I)[N+]([O-])=O)C(NC)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCCc1c(Cl)c(C(=O)NC)c([N+](=O)[O-])c(I)c1OC(N)=O", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "5058d372-6a3d-45ab-9cf8-a315378b2fe2", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCCCc1c(N(C)C)c(NC(C)=O)c(NC(N)=O)c(SC)c1C(C)(C)C", "smiles_random": "C(=O)(Nc1c(SC)c(C(C)(C)C)c(CCCC)c(c1NC(C)=O)N(C)C)N"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC(=O)(Nc1c(SC)c(C(C)(C)C)c(CCCC)c(c1NC(C)=O)N(C)C)N\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCCCc1c(N(C)C)c(NC(C)=O)c(NC(N)=O)c(SC)c1C(C)(C)C", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "3942474f-81a0-4431-bd1d-b0a1464288e9", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "C#CCc1c(I)c(OC)c(C(F)(F)F)c(CCC)c1SC", "smiles_random": "c1(c(c(c(C(F)(F)F)c(c1I)OC)CCC)SC)CC#C"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(c(c(c(C(F)(F)F)c(c1I)OC)CCC)SC)CC#C\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "C#CCc1c(I)c(OC)c(C(F)(F)F)c(CCC)c1SC", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "224973c6-f009-4099-8db7-3d647fd7050a", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCCc1c(I)c(C(=O)NC)c([N+](=O)[O-])c(O)c1NC", "smiles_random": "Ic1c(CCC)c(c(O)c([N+]([O-])=O)c1C(NC)=O)NC"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nIc1c(CCC)c(c(O)c([N+]([O-])=O)c1C(NC)=O)NC\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCCc1c(I)c(C(=O)NC)c([N+](=O)[O-])c(O)c1NC", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "77978ca3-5bf9-4e78-8f45-061c0ff5faaf", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "C=CCc1c(N(C)C)c(CC)c(C(C)=O)c(C=C)c1S(N)(=O)=O", "smiles_random": "c1(c(c(c(C(=O)C)c(c1S(N)(=O)=O)C=C)CC)N(C)C)CC=C"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(c(c(c(C(=O)C)c(c1S(N)(=O)=O)C=C)CC)N(C)C)CC=C\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "C=CCc1c(N(C)C)c(CC)c(C(C)=O)c(C=C)c1S(N)(=O)=O", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "be0d64c0-2187-48be-845a-04608943f257", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CNC(=O)c1c(S)c(C(F)(F)F)c(S(N)(=O)=O)c(C(C)(C)C)c1C1CCCCC1", "smiles_random": "C1CCCCC1c1c(c(S(N)(=O)=O)c(C(F)(F)F)c(c1C(=O)NC)S)C(C)(C)C"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC1CCCCC1c1c(c(S(N)(=O)=O)c(C(F)(F)F)c(c1C(=O)NC)S)C(C)(C)C\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CNC(=O)c1c(S)c(C(F)(F)F)c(S(N)(=O)=O)c(C(C)(C)C)c1C1CCCCC1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "9a570083-740e-4f73-80a1-a95f8f5c9ef9", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CNC(=O)c1c(O)c(OC)c(OC(N)=O)c(C)c1S", "smiles_random": "O=C(Oc1c(c(c(c(c1C)S)C(NC)=O)O)OC)N"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nO=C(Oc1c(c(c(c(c1C)S)C(NC)=O)O)OC)N\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CNC(=O)c1c(O)c(OC)c(OC(N)=O)c(C)c1S", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "ddfa8d8a-91a1-48ee-824a-34da6cc058ac", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "C#Cc1c(C#N)c(-c2ccccc2)c(C2CC2)c(C(F)(F)F)c1OC(N)=O", "smiles_random": "c1(C(F)(F)F)c(OC(=O)N)c(C#C)c(C#N)c(-c2ccccc2)c1C1CC1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(C(F)(F)F)c(OC(=O)N)c(C#C)c(C#N)c(-c2ccccc2)c1C1CC1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "C#Cc1c(C#N)c(-c2ccccc2)c(C2CC2)c(C(F)(F)F)c1OC(N)=O", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "0e3ac54a-2a9e-4afc-b077-0b7de90541ba", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "C=CCc1c(Br)c(NC)c(NC(C)=O)c(C(C)CC)c1CCCC", "smiles_random": "C(C=C)c1c(c(c(c(c1Br)NC)NC(=O)C)C(C)CC)CCCC"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC(C=C)c1c(c(c(c(c1Br)NC)NC(=O)C)C(C)CC)CCCC\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "C=CCc1c(Br)c(NC)c(NC(C)=O)c(C(C)CC)c1CCCC", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "ac290adf-7d20-472c-8dcb-1934fc3c9975", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "C=CCc1c(Br)c(NC(N)=O)c(N(C)C)c(C(C)C)c1NC(C)=O", "smiles_random": "C(=O)(N)Nc1c(Br)c(c(NC(C)=O)c(c1N(C)C)C(C)C)CC=C"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC(=O)(N)Nc1c(Br)c(c(NC(C)=O)c(c1N(C)C)C(C)C)CC=C\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "C=CCc1c(Br)c(NC(N)=O)c(N(C)C)c(C(C)C)c1NC(C)=O", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "293d2a0f-2fc5-4bf2-baa0-d74b2a806d73", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cc(Cl)ccc1I", "smiles_random": "c1c(c(I)ccc1Cl)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1c(c(I)ccc1Cl)F\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(Cl)ccc1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "a4d9c395-46d7-4e9b-b179-496bc7bf9c6a", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cc(Br)ccc1I", "smiles_random": "Ic1ccc(cc1F)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nIc1ccc(cc1F)Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(Br)ccc1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "5478a78f-f807-41e0-95b7-fd5456a5ebc0", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cc(Br)cc(I)c1", "smiles_random": "c1c(cc(F)cc1I)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1c(cc(F)cc1I)Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(Br)cc(I)c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "317e4ce6-62ca-487b-bbf3-247a94c58554", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cccc(I)c1Br", "smiles_random": "Brc1c(F)cccc1I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nBrc1c(F)cccc1I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cccc(I)c1Br", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "d8482e1a-ad3b-4962-a133-545a9ab27363", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Clc1ccc(I)cc1Br", "smiles_random": "c1(Cl)c(cc(cc1)I)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(Cl)c(cc(cc1)I)Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1ccc(I)cc1Br", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "40d6fa01-7bf8-4772-a6d7-7f6df1ef5d7e", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cccc(Cl)c1Br", "smiles_random": "c1c(c(Br)c(F)cc1)Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1c(c(Br)c(F)cc1)Cl\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cccc(Cl)c1Br", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "0b9fbbc4-4bc6-4e4b-940a-d9a226151f9b", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1ccc(Cl)c(I)c1", "smiles_random": "Fc1cc(I)c(cc1)Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cc(I)c(cc1)Cl\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1ccc(Cl)c(I)c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "56f84ba7-5625-4813-8a5d-fd08e8e5d520", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cccc(Br)c1Cl", "smiles_random": "c1(c(cccc1Br)F)Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(c(cccc1Br)F)Cl\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cccc(Br)c1Cl", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "a5df1f80-b9bf-4088-8af5-fb1579978f79", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cc(Br)ccc1I", "smiles_random": "c1(Br)cc(c(cc1)I)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(Br)cc(c(cc1)I)F\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(Br)ccc1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "0e2da586-7367-475e-b7ae-dbe3cabee613", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cc(Br)cc(I)c1", "smiles_random": "Fc1cc(cc(c1)Br)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cc(cc(c1)Br)I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(Br)cc(I)c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "da25c585-501b-4ba6-8f63-bce4a084c287", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cc(Cl)cc(Br)c1", "smiles_random": "Brc1cc(Cl)cc(c1)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nBrc1cc(Cl)cc(c1)F\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(Cl)cc(Br)c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "b44312b7-b9c4-4235-91a3-942fb4039ba5", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1ccc(I)c(Cl)c1", "smiles_random": "Clc1c(I)ccc(F)c1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nClc1c(I)ccc(F)c1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1ccc(I)c(Cl)c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "a812bf40-8de0-456f-bdd3-a0fe9791aaba", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cc(Cl)ccc1Br", "smiles_random": "Fc1cc(Cl)ccc1Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cc(Cl)ccc1Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(Cl)ccc1Br", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "2dc732cc-b318-4a83-8041-436bfcf4b69d", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Clc1ccc(Br)c(I)c1", "smiles_random": "c1c(cc(c(Br)c1)I)Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1c(cc(c(Br)c1)I)Cl\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1ccc(Br)c(I)c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "62c6288d-4b94-4821-a9c5-4095e4c6b7cb", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1ccc(Cl)cc1I", "smiles_random": "c1(ccc(Cl)cc1I)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(ccc(Cl)cc1I)F\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1ccc(Cl)cc1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "d553bbfe-7e2e-4fe4-893f-81f3f1b4176e", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Clc1cc(I)ccc1Br", "smiles_random": "c1(ccc(c(c1)Cl)Br)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(ccc(c(c1)Cl)Br)I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1cc(I)ccc1Br", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "718842fb-ef3b-42d9-bacd-77211799d3b1", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1c(Br)cccc1I", "smiles_random": "c1cc(I)c(c(Br)c1)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1cc(I)c(c(Br)c1)F\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1c(Br)cccc1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "a5574b35-8161-4d1b-bcae-99b6542235b2", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1ccc(I)c(Br)c1", "smiles_random": "c1c(F)cc(c(c1)I)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1c(F)cc(c(c1)I)Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1ccc(I)c(Br)c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "f03caf9d-02b6-45b8-a14a-28f161f0b3e9", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1ccc(Cl)cc1I", "smiles_random": "Fc1ccc(cc1I)Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1ccc(cc1I)Cl\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1ccc(Cl)cc1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "27665354-0557-416d-99c7-385840dc81ca", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1c(Br)cccc1I", "smiles_random": "Fc1c(I)cccc1Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1c(I)cccc1Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1c(Br)cccc1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "ed097023-940e-4912-936d-b6f227ccc0a2", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1ccnc(Cl)c1Br", "smiles_random": "c1nc(c(c(F)c1)Br)Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1nc(c(c(F)c1)Br)Cl\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1ccnc(Cl)c1Br", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "d6d08d12-d435-489d-8e40-642eb831f5d4", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cnc(Br)cc1Cl", "smiles_random": "c1c(Cl)c(F)cnc1Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1c(Cl)c(F)cnc1Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cnc(Br)cc1Cl", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "362103e3-2961-4afd-b71d-00a4c8d7a8ea", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cnc(Cl)cc1Br", "smiles_random": "n1c(Cl)cc(c(c1)F)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nn1c(Cl)cc(c(c1)F)Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cnc(Cl)cc1Br", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "282e36ef-7b62-485e-85ef-e369eb4f73b4", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1nccc(I)c1Br", "smiles_random": "Brc1c(I)ccnc1F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nBrc1c(I)ccnc1F\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1nccc(I)c1Br", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "2f0f666b-d719-4b19-bcb5-d240e0c06b11", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1ncc(Br)cc1I", "smiles_random": "c1c(Br)cc(c(F)n1)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1c(Br)cc(c(F)n1)I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1ncc(Br)cc1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "a3ba51cb-c458-4f90-89ed-9df2315cc0ce", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1ncc(I)cc1Br", "smiles_random": "Brc1cc(cnc1F)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nBrc1cc(cnc1F)I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1ncc(I)cc1Br", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "01aed562-1720-4fd0-8ed6-7cecc2ac6749", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cc(Br)c(I)cn1", "smiles_random": "c1(cc(c(I)cn1)Br)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(cc(c(I)cn1)Br)F\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(Br)c(I)cn1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "75110d62-c65a-4047-b00e-96a1afb488ee", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1nc(Br)ccc1I", "smiles_random": "Fc1c(ccc(n1)Br)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1c(ccc(n1)Br)I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1nc(Br)ccc1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "5a3e2481-77d8-4a55-bf73-f952bcef6306", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1ccc(I)nc1Cl", "smiles_random": "c1(Cl)c(F)ccc(n1)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(Cl)c(F)ccc(n1)I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1ccc(I)nc1Cl", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "be4b3a91-6bd5-4546-a666-d22c0522f80e", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Clc1nc(Br)ccc1I", "smiles_random": "c1(I)ccc(nc1Cl)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(I)ccc(nc1Cl)Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1nc(Br)ccc1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "f3caae87-a657-4e05-9067-08ac009f2275", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1ccc(I)c(Br)n1", "smiles_random": "n1c(F)ccc(c1Br)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nn1c(F)ccc(c1Br)I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1ccc(I)c(Br)n1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "4dc2613f-c82b-41c1-a8ca-8f3ce1b33b2f", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cc(I)c(Br)cn1", "smiles_random": "c1c(c(I)cc(n1)F)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1c(c(I)cc(n1)F)Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(I)c(Br)cn1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "6e980079-ce1b-4cbb-b2f4-98f41a59e16b", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Clc1cc(Br)ncc1I", "smiles_random": "Brc1cc(Cl)c(cn1)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nBrc1cc(Cl)c(cn1)I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1cc(Br)ncc1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "9564f4da-7739-4c03-9a77-22dd558a9d2d", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cnc(I)c(Br)c1", "smiles_random": "Brc1c(ncc(F)c1)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nBrc1c(ncc(F)c1)I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cnc(I)c(Br)c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "3a71806a-8c50-4bbb-af8f-678b5c83b01b", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cc(Cl)ncc1I", "smiles_random": "c1c(ncc(c1F)I)Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1c(ncc(c1F)I)Cl\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(Cl)ncc1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "0ae0943e-bca8-4fca-97f2-20865c55003e", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cncc(Cl)c1I", "smiles_random": "c1c(c(I)c(cn1)F)Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1c(c(I)c(cn1)F)Cl\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cncc(Cl)c1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "8aba9990-6ca3-48a5-b108-b62aaf7656ee", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cc(Cl)cc(Br)n1", "smiles_random": "c1c(nc(Br)cc1Cl)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1c(nc(Br)cc1Cl)F\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(Cl)cc(Br)n1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "a5123236-be36-44c0-b362-6cb0d9d94cf2", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cnc(Cl)cc1I", "smiles_random": "c1c(Cl)ncc(F)c1I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1c(Cl)ncc(F)c1I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cnc(Cl)cc1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "2d68927d-b199-486f-aa50-835b4ff96db3", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cc(Br)ncc1Cl", "smiles_random": "Brc1cc(c(cn1)Cl)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nBrc1cc(c(cn1)Cl)F\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(Br)ncc1Cl", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "4278ae6d-889b-4238-af74-0097278fed9d", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1nccc(Br)c1I", "smiles_random": "c1(c(F)nccc1Br)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(c(F)nccc1Br)I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1nccc(Br)c1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "fe232730-94fc-4713-9d14-42026b710b6a", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Fc1c(Br)noc1I", "smiles_random": "Fc1c(onc1Br)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1c(onc1Br)I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1c(Br)noc1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "5ca76cb0-d5f2-4aac-b6ce-4b7c636b24cc", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Fc1onc(Br)c1Cl", "smiles_random": "c1(Cl)c(onc1Br)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(Cl)c(onc1Br)F\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1onc(Br)c1Cl", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "45a80921-e527-48cf-a427-e67e3fb1f124", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Fc1noc(Cl)c1I", "smiles_random": "c1(Cl)onc(F)c1I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(Cl)onc(F)c1I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1noc(Cl)c1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "7a8996d3-9d30-4551-996e-d9f45fbd4934", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Fc1c(Br)noc1Cl", "smiles_random": "Brc1noc(Cl)c1F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nBrc1noc(Cl)c1F\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1c(Br)noc1Cl", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "91a269bf-e2aa-4cf3-b136-1642cb9a4b37", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Fc1c(Br)noc1I", "smiles_random": "n1c(c(c(I)o1)F)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nn1c(c(c(I)o1)F)Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1c(Br)noc1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "d5933413-bdec-43f5-bc9b-05230fe6b14a", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Fc1c(I)noc1Cl", "smiles_random": "c1(F)c(onc1I)Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(F)c(onc1I)Cl\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1c(I)noc1Cl", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "4b624740-a8dc-420d-a11f-a9f77e6339c0", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Fc1onc(I)c1Br", "smiles_random": "n1c(c(c(o1)F)Br)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nn1c(c(c(o1)F)Br)I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1onc(I)c1Br", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "072d04e1-36b3-4440-a528-100cbab38fab", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Clc1onc(I)c1Br", "smiles_random": "Brc1c(onc1I)Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nBrc1c(onc1I)Cl\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1onc(I)c1Br", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "326b2a58-8923-405f-994e-685bd3709d67", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Fc1noc(Cl)c1I", "smiles_random": "Clc1c(I)c(no1)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nClc1c(I)c(no1)F\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1noc(Cl)c1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "d7c1e095-a414-4332-a75e-21aff21d057f", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Clc1noc(I)c1Br", "smiles_random": "o1c(c(c(n1)Cl)Br)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\no1c(c(c(n1)Cl)Br)I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1noc(I)c1Br", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "477b3954-824e-49e3-83b1-c5b11d310405", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Fc1noc(I)c1Br", "smiles_random": "o1nc(c(Br)c1I)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\no1nc(c(Br)c1I)F\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1noc(I)c1Br", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "0103c17e-ec76-41ac-93dc-6b909abe5b57", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Fc1noc(Br)c1I", "smiles_random": "n1c(c(I)c(o1)Br)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nn1c(c(I)c(o1)Br)F\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1noc(Br)c1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "9cdefef7-62f4-4ace-bf39-22712f17515a", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Fc1onc(I)c1Cl", "smiles_random": "Ic1c(Cl)c(on1)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nIc1c(Cl)c(on1)F\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1onc(I)c1Cl", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "73919c58-6eaa-4200-9741-034a55b1328b", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Fc1c(Br)noc1Cl", "smiles_random": "n1c(Br)c(c(Cl)o1)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nn1c(Br)c(c(Cl)o1)F\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1c(Br)noc1Cl", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "39796b49-29a2-46fc-a5b7-9fde29eaac47", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Fc1noc(Br)c1I", "smiles_random": "n1oc(Br)c(c1F)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nn1oc(Br)c(c1F)I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1noc(Br)c1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "6dc7094d-1d2f-4dd0-9521-6e14a41fa72b", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Fc1noc(Br)c1I", "smiles_random": "Ic1c(noc1Br)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nIc1c(noc1Br)F\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1noc(Br)c1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "8bf78dcf-d21a-41b7-969d-6e1289dcd02a", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Fc1onc(Cl)c1Br", "smiles_random": "c1(Cl)noc(c1Br)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(Cl)noc(c1Br)F\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1onc(Cl)c1Br", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "41bd752c-798d-4cab-ad82-ba3ecd394a0d", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Clc1noc(Br)c1I", "smiles_random": "n1oc(Br)c(I)c1Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nn1oc(Br)c(I)c1Cl\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1noc(Br)c1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "4275b73c-f0a0-4572-8d23-9896285dec7b", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Clc1noc(Br)c1I", "smiles_random": "Clc1c(I)c(on1)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nClc1c(I)c(on1)Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1noc(Br)c1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "47458d44-98dd-4589-b9a9-b8b371cd8d5e", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Fc1c(Br)noc1I", "smiles_random": "c1(c(c(Br)no1)F)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(c(c(Br)no1)F)I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1c(Br)noc1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "b0b30027-b96c-4f7a-9ef4-26e23cbb51e5", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Fc1cccc2c(Br)cc(I)cc12", "smiles_random": "c12c(c(F)ccc1)cc(I)cc2Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc12c(c(F)ccc1)cc(I)cc2Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cccc2c(Br)cc(I)cc12", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "acedb5c8-2d49-405b-851c-1b6ff586a0f5", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Fc1cc(I)cc2c(Cl)cccc12", "smiles_random": "c1c2c(cc(cc2F)I)c(Cl)cc1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1c2c(cc(cc2F)I)c(Cl)cc1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(I)cc2c(Cl)cccc12", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "9ca8a6a0-7e00-4d4f-a1cb-0d015f07dc9f", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Fc1ccc2c(I)cccc2c1Cl", "smiles_random": "c1c2c(c(F)ccc2c(cc1)I)Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1c2c(c(F)ccc2c(cc1)I)Cl\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1ccc2c(I)cccc2c1Cl", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "aa01c4ce-7255-4ab7-a154-02e738b3d2b7", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Fc1cc(Br)c(Cl)c2ccccc12", "smiles_random": "c12c(c(F)cc(c2Cl)Br)cccc1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc12c(c(F)cc(c2Cl)Br)cccc1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(Br)c(Cl)c2ccccc12", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "af24632b-7193-40f1-94f8-858e35192126", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Clc1cc(I)cc2c(Br)cccc12", "smiles_random": "c1(cc2c(cccc2Br)c(c1)Cl)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(cc2c(cccc2Br)c(c1)Cl)I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1cc(I)cc2c(Br)cccc12", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "b999adad-63d4-44bd-b691-b18a305a6349", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Clc1c(I)ccc2cc(Br)ccc12", "smiles_random": "Clc1c2ccc(cc2ccc1I)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nClc1c2ccc(cc2ccc1I)Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1c(I)ccc2cc(Br)ccc12", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "14a59fb5-816a-4f87-a5ae-46c60b2aec83", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Fc1cccc2c(Br)c(I)ccc12", "smiles_random": "Fc1c2ccc(I)c(Br)c2ccc1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1c2ccc(I)c(Br)c2ccc1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cccc2c(Br)c(I)ccc12", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "0ea78912-4f7b-46f1-ae6a-c220deb45a92", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Clc1c(Br)cc(I)c2ccccc12", "smiles_random": "Ic1cc(c(c2ccccc12)Cl)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nIc1cc(c(c2ccccc12)Cl)Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1c(Br)cc(I)c2ccccc12", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "1f31baee-665f-4c94-8626-85858f057404", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Fc1cc(Br)c2cc(Cl)ccc2c1", "smiles_random": "c1c(F)cc(Br)c2c1ccc(Cl)c2"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1c(F)cc(Br)c2c1ccc(Cl)c2\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(Br)c2cc(Cl)ccc2c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "5e1ebff2-6cef-496c-81c4-d584d5308f9d", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Clc1cccc2ccc(Br)c(I)c12", "smiles_random": "c12ccc(c(c2c(Cl)ccc1)I)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc12ccc(c(c2c(Cl)ccc1)I)Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1cccc2ccc(Br)c(I)c12", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "6edd7470-f65f-4f38-b080-2d3f018d120e", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Fc1cc(I)c2cc(Cl)ccc2c1", "smiles_random": "Ic1cc(F)cc2ccc(cc12)Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nIc1cc(F)cc2ccc(cc12)Cl\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(I)c2cc(Cl)ccc2c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "97ddee6b-f30c-4712-9ae8-eca891fabfc2", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Fc1cc(I)c2c(Br)cccc2c1", "smiles_random": "c1ccc(Br)c2c1cc(F)cc2I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1ccc(Br)c2c1cc(F)cc2I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(I)c2c(Br)cccc2c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "15e313a1-0104-4773-9646-3da5e5a60ca0", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Fc1cc2ccc(Cl)cc2cc1I", "smiles_random": "c1c(c(cc2cc(ccc12)Cl)I)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1c(c(cc2cc(ccc12)Cl)I)F\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc2ccc(Cl)cc2cc1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "5cced612-e98c-4e9c-9242-459d7f4b0ed5", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Fc1cccc2cc(I)cc(Cl)c12", "smiles_random": "c1c(Cl)c2c(cc1I)cccc2F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1c(Cl)c2c(cc1I)cccc2F\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cccc2cc(I)cc(Cl)c12", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "4c869625-0c8e-40ce-9f4c-46795461a3a8", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Fc1cccc2ccc(I)c(Cl)c12", "smiles_random": "c1cc2c(c(Cl)c1I)c(ccc2)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1cc2c(c(Cl)c1I)c(ccc2)F\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cccc2ccc(I)c(Cl)c12", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "20e213ee-a14f-4cc9-9eac-c52af6bf3f79", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Fc1cc2cccc(I)c2cc1Br", "smiles_random": "c1(c(cc2c(c1)c(I)ccc2)F)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(c(cc2c(c1)c(I)ccc2)F)Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc2cccc(I)c2cc1Br", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "68caf450-0fc9-4896-9ca1-ed7853591b8e", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Fc1cc(I)c2cc(Br)ccc2c1", "smiles_random": "c1(ccc2c(c1)c(cc(c2)F)I)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(ccc2c(c1)c(cc(c2)F)I)Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(I)c2cc(Br)ccc2c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "7adb3d41-6320-40ba-889f-2a6e58326a46", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Clc1cc(I)c2ccc(Br)cc2c1", "smiles_random": "c1(Cl)cc2c(c(I)c1)ccc(Br)c2"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(Cl)cc2c(c(I)c1)ccc(Br)c2\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1cc(I)c2ccc(Br)cc2c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "4f020441-992f-45c4-a662-9f1e81a4904a", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Clc1ccc2cc(Br)c(I)cc2c1", "smiles_random": "c1c(Cl)cc2c(c1)cc(c(I)c2)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1c(Cl)cc2c(c1)cc(c(I)c2)Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1ccc2cc(Br)c(I)cc2c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "1de15e69-ce1f-43dd-9027-a2020f5c49f1", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Clc1ccc2cccc(I)c2c1Br", "smiles_random": "Ic1cccc2ccc(Cl)c(Br)c21"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nIc1cccc2ccc(Cl)c(Br)c21\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1ccc2cccc(I)c2c1Br", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "48a9dad6-fbfb-4e90-abfb-38baed4a6b75", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Clc1nc2cc(I)ccc2cc1Br", "smiles_random": "c12c(cc(cc1)I)nc(c(c2)Br)Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc12c(cc(cc1)I)nc(c(c2)Br)Cl\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1nc2cc(I)ccc2cc1Br", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "178c9fbd-e2e4-4cf0-9119-7b71f519ed45", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Fc1ccnc2c(I)c(Cl)ccc12", "smiles_random": "c1nc2c(c(F)c1)ccc(Cl)c2I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1nc2c(c(F)c1)ccc(Cl)c2I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1ccnc2c(I)c(Cl)ccc12", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "2c9fac42-1c2a-420b-aed8-b6bb70b079c1", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Clc1ccc2c(Br)ccnc2c1I", "smiles_random": "c1c2c(ccnc2c(I)c(c1)Cl)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1c2c(ccnc2c(I)c(c1)Cl)Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1ccc2c(Br)ccnc2c1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "e55d3af9-61f0-4d0a-a594-09fe92ea98a0", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Fc1cnc2ccc(Cl)c(I)c2c1", "smiles_random": "c1c(F)cnc2ccc(c(c12)I)Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1c(F)cnc2ccc(c(c12)I)Cl\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cnc2ccc(Cl)c(I)c2c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "886989ee-61c1-4309-bd9a-8cc6037c29d3", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Fc1ccc2ncc(I)c(Br)c2c1", "smiles_random": "c1c(ccc2c1c(Br)c(cn2)I)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1c(ccc2c1c(Br)c(cn2)I)F\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1ccc2ncc(I)c(Br)c2c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "2fafc6eb-dce0-4565-97d7-584b209197e9", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Fc1cccc2nc(I)cc(Cl)c12", "smiles_random": "c1ccc(c2c1nc(cc2Cl)I)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1ccc(c2c1nc(cc2Cl)I)F\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cccc2nc(I)cc(Cl)c12", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "dd5561e0-d064-4490-a9e3-a65df8fb1f57", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Fc1cc2cccnc2c(I)c1Cl", "smiles_random": "Fc1c(Cl)c(c2c(c1)cccn2)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1c(Cl)c(c2c(c1)cccn2)I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc2cccnc2c(I)c1Cl", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "842d1686-31c5-4d09-80c8-591ed446c3de", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Fc1cccc2nc(Br)cc(Cl)c12", "smiles_random": "Clc1cc(nc2c1c(F)ccc2)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nClc1cc(nc2c1c(F)ccc2)Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cccc2nc(Br)cc(Cl)c12", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "29317fea-93ed-4e72-93ea-6c674b073964", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Fc1cc(Cl)c2nc(Br)ccc2c1", "smiles_random": "n1c2c(cc(cc2Cl)F)ccc1Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nn1c2c(cc(cc2Cl)F)ccc1Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(Cl)c2nc(Br)ccc2c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "afbfee7b-3a17-4b7a-b577-042b5ac8da33", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Fc1c(Br)cnc2c(I)cccc12", "smiles_random": "c1nc2c(cccc2c(F)c1Br)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1nc2c(cccc2c(F)c1Br)I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1c(Br)cnc2c(I)cccc12", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "47a81cd1-681d-4e7f-a94f-de921406f155", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Fc1cc2c(Br)cccc2nc1I", "smiles_random": "Brc1cccc2c1cc(F)c(I)n2"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nBrc1cccc2c1cc(F)c(I)n2\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc2c(Br)cccc2nc1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "9181e1e2-44f9-4017-814e-99688ea4d98c", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Clc1cc(Br)cc2ncc(I)cc12", "smiles_random": "c1c(cc(c2cc(I)cnc12)Cl)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1c(cc(c2cc(I)cnc12)Cl)Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1cc(Br)cc2ncc(I)cc12", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "8159f3fe-a99b-45a6-b301-0ae2649044ad", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Clc1ccc2ccc(I)c(Br)c2n1", "smiles_random": "Ic1ccc2ccc(Cl)nc2c1Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nIc1ccc2ccc(Cl)nc2c1Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1ccc2ccc(I)c(Br)c2n1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "5c9678d4-7bd3-4526-9f76-f4350d804a20", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Fc1ccc2c(Br)c(I)ccc2n1", "smiles_random": "c12c(c(Br)c(I)cc1)ccc(n2)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc12c(c(Br)c(I)cc1)ccc(n2)F\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1ccc2c(Br)c(I)ccc2n1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "ebe46414-3856-4ce0-b6ae-caf76d8b12ba", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Clc1ccnc2cc(I)cc(Br)c12", "smiles_random": "c1(Br)c2c(ccnc2cc(c1)I)Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(Br)c2c(ccnc2cc(c1)I)Cl\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1ccnc2cc(I)cc(Br)c12", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "cc74a57c-3ffd-4cd3-b195-1036cfc9c226", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Fc1cc(Cl)c2cc(I)ccc2n1", "smiles_random": "c12nc(F)cc(c1cc(cc2)I)Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc12nc(F)cc(c1cc(cc2)I)Cl\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(Cl)c2cc(I)ccc2n1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "75f04104-088a-407e-946d-b3bd7f8e5325", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Fc1ccc2nc(Br)ccc2c1Cl", "smiles_random": "Fc1ccc2c(c1Cl)ccc(n2)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1ccc2c(c1Cl)ccc(n2)Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1ccc2nc(Br)ccc2c1Cl", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "1539b485-dc62-4c45-b5e7-e77d16d38882", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Clc1cc(Br)c2cccc(I)c2n1", "smiles_random": "c1(cc(Br)c2c(n1)c(I)ccc2)Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(cc(Br)c2c(n1)c(I)ccc2)Cl\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1cc(Br)c2cccc(I)c2n1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "de907f0a-452b-4edc-9fc4-c7a7e6cee4bc", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Fc1cccc2c(Br)cc(I)nc12", "smiles_random": "c1cc(c2c(c(cc(I)n2)Br)c1)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1cc(c2c(c(cc(I)n2)Br)c1)F\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cccc2c(Br)cc(I)nc12", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "3cb80434-90fc-4f8b-a41b-a514d037768a", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_random", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Fc1nc2ccccc2c(Br)c1Cl", "smiles_random": "c1ccc2c(Br)c(Cl)c(F)nc2c1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1ccc2c(Br)c(Cl)c(F)nc2c1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1nc2ccccc2c(Br)c1Cl", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "d3b4868c-219f-4601-9d85-5d6c35b19648", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_canonical", "meta_data": {"smiles": "C=CCc1c(C=O)c(C(C)CC)c(F)c(NC)c1OC(N)=O", "smiles_random": "c1(c(CC=C)c(C=O)c(C(CC)C)c(c1NC)F)OC(N)=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC=CCc1c(C=O)c(C(C)CC)c(F)c(NC)c1OC(N)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "C=CCc1c(C=O)c(C(C)CC)c(F)c(NC)c1OC(N)=O", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "6b10a1d1-dd46-4e0c-86ec-bc436d0f109e", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_canonical", "meta_data": {"smiles": "C=CCc1c(OC)c(I)c(C(C)C)c(C#N)c1C1CCCCC1", "smiles_random": "C(C=C)c1c(OC)c(c(c(C#N)c1C1CCCCC1)C(C)C)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC=CCc1c(OC)c(I)c(C(C)C)c(C#N)c1C1CCCCC1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "C=CCc1c(OC)c(I)c(C(C)C)c(C#N)c1C1CCCCC1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "fb5d06be-819b-4ae2-92a2-fb8110059423", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_canonical", "meta_data": {"smiles": "C#CCc1c(Br)c(C(C)C)c(NC(N)=O)c(CC=C)c1S(N)(=O)=O", "smiles_random": "C(C)(C)c1c(c(c(S(=O)(N)=O)c(c1Br)CC#C)CC=C)NC(=O)N"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC#CCc1c(Br)c(C(C)C)c(NC(N)=O)c(CC=C)c1S(N)(=O)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "C#CCc1c(Br)c(C(C)C)c(NC(N)=O)c(CC=C)c1S(N)(=O)=O", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "584830af-8132-494e-bc8a-a227703eb568", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_canonical", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCCc1c(S(N)(=O)=O)c(NC(N)=O)c(C#N)c(C2CCCCC2)c1S(=O)(=O)O", "smiles_random": "O=C(N)Nc1c(S(N)(=O)=O)c(c(c(C2CCCCC2)c1C#N)S(=O)(=O)O)CCC"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nCCCc1c(S(N)(=O)=O)c(NC(N)=O)c(C#N)c(C2CCCCC2)c1S(=O)(=O)O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCCc1c(S(N)(=O)=O)c(NC(N)=O)c(C#N)c(C2CCCCC2)c1S(=O)(=O)O", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "85f149b6-e8c4-42c0-9eed-0462304faed6", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_canonical", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCc1c(C(=O)OC(C)=O)c(Cl)c(NC(N)=O)c(-c2ccccc2)c1C(C)C", "smiles_random": "O=C(OC(=O)C)c1c(CC)c(c(c(c1Cl)NC(=O)N)-c1ccccc1)C(C)C"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nCCc1c(C(=O)OC(C)=O)c(Cl)c(NC(N)=O)c(-c2ccccc2)c1C(C)C\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCc1c(C(=O)OC(C)=O)c(Cl)c(NC(N)=O)c(-c2ccccc2)c1C(C)C", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "2d4175aa-3d4a-49f7-a169-248af4b6be95", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_canonical", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCC(C)c1c(SC)c(C(=O)O)c(C#N)c(Br)c1C(=O)OC", "smiles_random": "OC(c1c(c(Br)c(C(=O)OC)c(C(CC)C)c1SC)C#N)=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nCCC(C)c1c(SC)c(C(=O)O)c(C#N)c(Br)c1C(=O)OC\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCC(C)c1c(SC)c(C(=O)O)c(C#N)c(Br)c1C(=O)OC", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "9446ccf2-0c06-40f3-bcf6-4b1925fc165d", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_canonical", "meta_data": {"smiles": "C#CCc1c(CCCC)c(Br)c(N)c(C=O)c1NC", "smiles_random": "c1(c(c(NC)c(CC#C)c(CCCC)c1Br)C=O)N"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC#CCc1c(CCCC)c(Br)c(N)c(C=O)c1NC\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "C#CCc1c(CCCC)c(Br)c(N)c(C=O)c1NC", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "6cf551fb-215e-4ff5-9684-321136b39ebe", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_canonical", "meta_data": {"smiles": "C#Cc1c(NC(C)=O)c(Cl)c(C(C)CC)c(S(N)(=O)=O)c1-c1ccccc1", "smiles_random": "NS(=O)(=O)c1c(-c2ccccc2)c(c(NC(=O)C)c(Cl)c1C(CC)C)C#C"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC#Cc1c(NC(C)=O)c(Cl)c(C(C)CC)c(S(N)(=O)=O)c1-c1ccccc1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "C#Cc1c(NC(C)=O)c(Cl)c(C(C)CC)c(S(N)(=O)=O)c1-c1ccccc1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "8c1a6436-f174-4856-9036-4f3a94732ac1", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_canonical", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CC(=O)Nc1c(C=O)c(N(C)C)c(S(=O)(=O)O)c(C(F)(F)F)c1OC(N)=O", "smiles_random": "C(=O)c1c(N(C)C)c(S(=O)(O)=O)c(c(OC(=O)N)c1NC(=O)C)C(F)(F)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nCC(=O)Nc1c(C=O)c(N(C)C)c(S(=O)(=O)O)c(C(F)(F)F)c1OC(N)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CC(=O)Nc1c(C=O)c(N(C)C)c(S(=O)(=O)O)c(C(F)(F)F)c1OC(N)=O", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "9b29c9d1-2a4f-4652-9e8d-b96a5d77ec45", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_canonical", "meta_data": {"smiles": "C=CCc1c(C(C)=O)c(Br)c(C(=O)NC)c(CC)c1S(N)(=O)=O", "smiles_random": "C(Cc1c(c(c(c(Br)c1C(=O)C)C(NC)=O)CC)S(=O)(N)=O)=C"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC=CCc1c(C(C)=O)c(Br)c(C(=O)NC)c(CC)c1S(N)(=O)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "C=CCc1c(C(C)=O)c(Br)c(C(=O)NC)c(CC)c1S(N)(=O)=O", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "75c946e2-8bf0-4293-b885-eeaefba81fef", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_canonical", "meta_data": {"smiles": "C#CCc1c(C(=O)O)c(C(C)CC)c(SC)c(C2CCCCC2)c1C(=O)NC", "smiles_random": "S(C)c1c(C2CCCCC2)c(C(=O)NC)c(c(C(=O)O)c1C(C)CC)CC#C"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC#CCc1c(C(=O)O)c(C(C)CC)c(SC)c(C2CCCCC2)c1C(=O)NC\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "C#CCc1c(C(=O)O)c(C(C)CC)c(SC)c(C2CCCCC2)c1C(=O)NC", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "f5328607-36a3-43f0-a1c1-0f863eb41cc9", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_canonical", "meta_data": {"smiles": "C#Cc1c(F)c(C=C)c(C#N)c(CC=C)c1Br", "smiles_random": "c1(C=C)c(F)c(C#C)c(c(c1C#N)CC=C)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC#Cc1c(F)c(C=C)c(C#N)c(CC=C)c1Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "C#Cc1c(F)c(C=C)c(C#N)c(CC=C)c1Br", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "c9188484-661d-48c8-aa75-b89f46d3856c", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_canonical", "meta_data": {"smiles": "C#CCc1c(NC(N)=O)c(C(=O)NC)c(CCCC)c(N(C)C)c1C(=O)OC(C)=O", "smiles_random": "C(=O)(C)OC(c1c(c(c(c(CCCC)c1N(C)C)C(=O)NC)NC(=O)N)CC#C)=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC#CCc1c(NC(N)=O)c(C(=O)NC)c(CCCC)c(N(C)C)c1C(=O)OC(C)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "C#CCc1c(NC(N)=O)c(C(=O)NC)c(CCCC)c(N(C)C)c1C(=O)OC(C)=O", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "f2fec9e2-77af-4a0f-ab74-a6041f9fa229", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_canonical", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCCc1c(C)c(C(C)(C)C)c(NC)c(C2CC2)c1S(N)(=O)=O", "smiles_random": "O=S(N)(c1c(c(NC)c(C(C)(C)C)c(C)c1CCC)C1CC1)=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nCCCc1c(C)c(C(C)(C)C)c(NC)c(C2CC2)c1S(N)(=O)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCCc1c(C)c(C(C)(C)C)c(NC)c(C2CC2)c1S(N)(=O)=O", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "b88e41aa-d62f-4f93-a0bb-28e7bc609369", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_canonical", "meta_data": {"smiles": "NC(=O)Nc1c(F)c(Cl)c(S)c(S(=O)(=O)O)c1[N+](=O)[O-]", "smiles_random": "O=S(O)(=O)c1c(c(Cl)c(c(NC(N)=O)c1[N+](=O)[O-])F)S"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nNC(=O)Nc1c(F)c(Cl)c(S)c(S(=O)(=O)O)c1[N+](=O)[O-]\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "NC(=O)Nc1c(F)c(Cl)c(S)c(S(=O)(=O)O)c1[N+](=O)[O-]", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "36915a43-6f90-43f4-a6b6-abaf599c6049", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_canonical", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCCCc1c(NC(N)=O)c(NC)c(F)c([N+](=O)[O-])c1C(C)CC", "smiles_random": "CCCCc1c(NC(=O)N)c(c(F)c([N+]([O-])=O)c1C(CC)C)NC"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nCCCCc1c(NC(N)=O)c(NC)c(F)c([N+](=O)[O-])c1C(C)CC\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCCCc1c(NC(N)=O)c(NC)c(F)c([N+](=O)[O-])c1C(C)CC", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "08d5015b-59fe-4bd2-a259-9735e159bd4c", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_canonical", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CC(C)(C)c1c(Cl)c(C(=O)O)c(-c2ccccc2)c(C(F)(F)F)c1C#N", "smiles_random": "c1ccccc1-c1c(c(c(C(C)(C)C)c(Cl)c1C(O)=O)C#N)C(F)(F)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nCC(C)(C)c1c(Cl)c(C(=O)O)c(-c2ccccc2)c(C(F)(F)F)c1C#N\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CC(C)(C)c1c(Cl)c(C(=O)O)c(-c2ccccc2)c(C(F)(F)F)c1C#N", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "a62c78ea-8386-44e0-808a-dc4807bb8499", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_canonical", "meta_data": {"smiles": "C#Cc1c(CC(C)C)c(NC(N)=O)c(C(=O)OC(C)=O)c(C)c1C(C)=O", "smiles_random": "O=C(Nc1c(CC(C)C)c(c(C(C)=O)c(c1C(=O)OC(C)=O)C)C#C)N"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC#Cc1c(CC(C)C)c(NC(N)=O)c(C(=O)OC(C)=O)c(C)c1C(C)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "C#Cc1c(CC(C)C)c(NC(N)=O)c(C(=O)OC(C)=O)c(C)c1C(C)=O", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "bd02acf6-bd0f-46d1-afcc-7ed14c82d629", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_canonical", "meta_data": {"smiles": "C#Cc1c(C2CCCCC2)c(N)c(Br)c(S(=O)(=O)O)c1C(F)(F)F", "smiles_random": "Brc1c(c(C2CCCCC2)c(c(c1S(O)(=O)=O)C(F)(F)F)C#C)N"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC#Cc1c(C2CCCCC2)c(N)c(Br)c(S(=O)(=O)O)c1C(F)(F)F\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "C#Cc1c(C2CCCCC2)c(N)c(Br)c(S(=O)(=O)O)c1C(F)(F)F", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "d3bda6c7-9f6a-4655-8929-379ba35aa485", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_canonical", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CNc1c(S)c(C=O)c(Br)c(C2CCCCC2)c1C(=O)O", "smiles_random": "C1CCCC(c2c(c(C=O)c(c(c2C(O)=O)NC)S)Br)C1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nCNc1c(S)c(C=O)c(Br)c(C2CCCCC2)c1C(=O)O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CNc1c(S)c(C=O)c(Br)c(C2CCCCC2)c1C(=O)O", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "d1b2aa00-0bd1-4bd4-b942-4ec83e9c9a27", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_canonical", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCCc1c(Cl)c(C(=O)NC)c([N+](=O)[O-])c(I)c1OC(N)=O", "smiles_random": "c1(Cl)c(c(c(c(c1CCC)OC(N)=O)I)[N+]([O-])=O)C(NC)=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nCCCc1c(Cl)c(C(=O)NC)c([N+](=O)[O-])c(I)c1OC(N)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCCc1c(Cl)c(C(=O)NC)c([N+](=O)[O-])c(I)c1OC(N)=O", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "01194557-a55a-4b2d-b799-5d5996232503", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_canonical", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCCCc1c(N(C)C)c(NC(C)=O)c(NC(N)=O)c(SC)c1C(C)(C)C", "smiles_random": "C(=O)(Nc1c(SC)c(C(C)(C)C)c(CCCC)c(c1NC(C)=O)N(C)C)N"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nCCCCc1c(N(C)C)c(NC(C)=O)c(NC(N)=O)c(SC)c1C(C)(C)C\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCCCc1c(N(C)C)c(NC(C)=O)c(NC(N)=O)c(SC)c1C(C)(C)C", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "686fef97-f214-46f4-ac31-68db8d1c5241", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_canonical", "meta_data": {"smiles": "C#CCc1c(I)c(OC)c(C(F)(F)F)c(CCC)c1SC", "smiles_random": "c1(c(c(c(C(F)(F)F)c(c1I)OC)CCC)SC)CC#C"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC#CCc1c(I)c(OC)c(C(F)(F)F)c(CCC)c1SC\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "C#CCc1c(I)c(OC)c(C(F)(F)F)c(CCC)c1SC", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "bea0ae6c-f68a-4fe9-8410-8e529d438bf6", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_canonical", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCCc1c(I)c(C(=O)NC)c([N+](=O)[O-])c(O)c1NC", "smiles_random": "Ic1c(CCC)c(c(O)c([N+]([O-])=O)c1C(NC)=O)NC"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nCCCc1c(I)c(C(=O)NC)c([N+](=O)[O-])c(O)c1NC\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCCc1c(I)c(C(=O)NC)c([N+](=O)[O-])c(O)c1NC", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "09e95e92-531f-422d-aefe-31bf676721c1", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_canonical", "meta_data": {"smiles": "C=CCc1c(N(C)C)c(CC)c(C(C)=O)c(C=C)c1S(N)(=O)=O", "smiles_random": "c1(c(c(c(C(=O)C)c(c1S(N)(=O)=O)C=C)CC)N(C)C)CC=C"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC=CCc1c(N(C)C)c(CC)c(C(C)=O)c(C=C)c1S(N)(=O)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "C=CCc1c(N(C)C)c(CC)c(C(C)=O)c(C=C)c1S(N)(=O)=O", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "c4e7b653-e84d-401f-83a8-b548af88d796", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_canonical", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CNC(=O)c1c(S)c(C(F)(F)F)c(S(N)(=O)=O)c(C(C)(C)C)c1C1CCCCC1", "smiles_random": "C1CCCCC1c1c(c(S(N)(=O)=O)c(C(F)(F)F)c(c1C(=O)NC)S)C(C)(C)C"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nCNC(=O)c1c(S)c(C(F)(F)F)c(S(N)(=O)=O)c(C(C)(C)C)c1C1CCCCC1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CNC(=O)c1c(S)c(C(F)(F)F)c(S(N)(=O)=O)c(C(C)(C)C)c1C1CCCCC1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "0e8e1d0a-eecf-4b44-aae3-a1bf44d815c2", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_canonical", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CNC(=O)c1c(O)c(OC)c(OC(N)=O)c(C)c1S", "smiles_random": "O=C(Oc1c(c(c(c(c1C)S)C(NC)=O)O)OC)N"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nCNC(=O)c1c(O)c(OC)c(OC(N)=O)c(C)c1S\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CNC(=O)c1c(O)c(OC)c(OC(N)=O)c(C)c1S", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "6ff550e2-8474-4e20-bcf4-8622e72e1a65", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_canonical", "meta_data": {"smiles": "C#Cc1c(C#N)c(-c2ccccc2)c(C2CC2)c(C(F)(F)F)c1OC(N)=O", "smiles_random": "c1(C(F)(F)F)c(OC(=O)N)c(C#C)c(C#N)c(-c2ccccc2)c1C1CC1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC#Cc1c(C#N)c(-c2ccccc2)c(C2CC2)c(C(F)(F)F)c1OC(N)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "C#Cc1c(C#N)c(-c2ccccc2)c(C2CC2)c(C(F)(F)F)c1OC(N)=O", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "0d436f2f-9f80-4658-9369-62cf384389ed", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_canonical", "meta_data": {"smiles": "C=CCc1c(Br)c(NC)c(NC(C)=O)c(C(C)CC)c1CCCC", "smiles_random": "C(C=C)c1c(c(c(c(c1Br)NC)NC(=O)C)C(C)CC)CCCC"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC=CCc1c(Br)c(NC)c(NC(C)=O)c(C(C)CC)c1CCCC\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "C=CCc1c(Br)c(NC)c(NC(C)=O)c(C(C)CC)c1CCCC", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "1e1d78bd-6174-43ca-a574-451344c204e6", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "FG_canonical", "meta_data": {"smiles": "C=CCc1c(Br)c(NC(N)=O)c(N(C)C)c(C(C)C)c1NC(C)=O", "smiles_random": "C(=O)(N)Nc1c(Br)c(c(NC(C)=O)c(c1N(C)C)C(C)C)CC=C"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC=CCc1c(Br)c(NC(N)=O)c(N(C)C)c(C(C)C)c1NC(C)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "C=CCc1c(Br)c(NC(N)=O)c(N(C)C)c(C(C)C)c1NC(C)=O", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "4e80406b-239b-410c-afb3-3c6d553f7d4a", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cc(Cl)ccc1I", "smiles_random": "c1c(c(I)ccc1Cl)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cc(Cl)ccc1I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(Cl)ccc1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "e7e5c912-c780-4579-a162-76fde928b97e", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cc(Br)ccc1I", "smiles_random": "Ic1ccc(cc1F)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cc(Br)ccc1I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(Br)ccc1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "7fc84d9e-f0bd-4c2d-a2ee-106190178b6a", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cc(Br)cc(I)c1", "smiles_random": "c1c(cc(F)cc1I)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cc(Br)cc(I)c1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(Br)cc(I)c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "616680f0-2a7a-4ea7-965b-8543a5f02845", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cccc(I)c1Br", "smiles_random": "Brc1c(F)cccc1I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cccc(I)c1Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cccc(I)c1Br", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "5ce5240d-3126-4a98-837c-ad86a801f09a", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Clc1ccc(I)cc1Br", "smiles_random": "c1(Cl)c(cc(cc1)I)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nClc1ccc(I)cc1Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1ccc(I)cc1Br", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "c9c16996-e591-41e0-8e65-e81ee1a80772", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cccc(Cl)c1Br", "smiles_random": "c1c(c(Br)c(F)cc1)Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cccc(Cl)c1Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cccc(Cl)c1Br", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "8a6fbfa8-f771-4b7a-87a2-7116e119c182", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1ccc(Cl)c(I)c1", "smiles_random": "Fc1cc(I)c(cc1)Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1ccc(Cl)c(I)c1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1ccc(Cl)c(I)c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "c4f72987-4f87-4178-a536-f62efc02a8c2", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cccc(Br)c1Cl", "smiles_random": "c1(c(cccc1Br)F)Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cccc(Br)c1Cl\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cccc(Br)c1Cl", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "c56b57a2-e521-442e-a4b2-bd20eccff293", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cc(Br)ccc1I", "smiles_random": "c1(Br)cc(c(cc1)I)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cc(Br)ccc1I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(Br)ccc1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "ebec938d-a30a-4a25-8bda-1e4e35a589c5", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cc(Br)cc(I)c1", "smiles_random": "Fc1cc(cc(c1)Br)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cc(Br)cc(I)c1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(Br)cc(I)c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "da6d0c61-0279-43dc-8950-f9d8e49fcbcc", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cc(Cl)cc(Br)c1", "smiles_random": "Brc1cc(Cl)cc(c1)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cc(Cl)cc(Br)c1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(Cl)cc(Br)c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "76ce46ac-b25f-4452-b9dc-0e1248dbf79e", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1ccc(I)c(Cl)c1", "smiles_random": "Clc1c(I)ccc(F)c1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1ccc(I)c(Cl)c1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1ccc(I)c(Cl)c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "055f402b-06bf-4b55-96d4-677fd6a4d3c3", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cc(Cl)ccc1Br", "smiles_random": "Fc1cc(Cl)ccc1Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cc(Cl)ccc1Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(Cl)ccc1Br", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "5199b4d9-5e39-4816-ab50-f4ccf8099ad7", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Clc1ccc(Br)c(I)c1", "smiles_random": "c1c(cc(c(Br)c1)I)Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nClc1ccc(Br)c(I)c1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1ccc(Br)c(I)c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "04f61dcf-ca6f-4e1c-8a7e-4fef6bb5fd33", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1ccc(Cl)cc1I", "smiles_random": "c1(ccc(Cl)cc1I)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1ccc(Cl)cc1I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1ccc(Cl)cc1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "9d822926-e5c6-4711-9a27-328931af0fff", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Clc1cc(I)ccc1Br", "smiles_random": "c1(ccc(c(c1)Cl)Br)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nClc1cc(I)ccc1Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1cc(I)ccc1Br", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "d087f0ea-4477-4c04-bce5-9c67f3bb2546", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1c(Br)cccc1I", "smiles_random": "c1cc(I)c(c(Br)c1)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1c(Br)cccc1I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1c(Br)cccc1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "a9308fa3-0723-4815-84fd-0ae23d15e347", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1ccc(I)c(Br)c1", "smiles_random": "c1c(F)cc(c(c1)I)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1ccc(I)c(Br)c1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1ccc(I)c(Br)c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "19a028b6-06a5-4c99-9953-c48c311b4a46", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1ccc(Cl)cc1I", "smiles_random": "Fc1ccc(cc1I)Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1ccc(Cl)cc1I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1ccc(Cl)cc1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "2457ba10-6f02-406b-bbc8-60a6d86bbe11", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Benzene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Benzene", "scaffold_smiles": "c1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1c(Br)cccc1I", "smiles_random": "Fc1c(I)cccc1Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1c(Br)cccc1I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1c(Br)cccc1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "d17ddaa9-d741-4693-85ba-a7ac279c087a", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1ccnc(Cl)c1Br", "smiles_random": "c1nc(c(c(F)c1)Br)Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1ccnc(Cl)c1Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1ccnc(Cl)c1Br", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "80898c20-12a9-41f2-a9ae-de1574fae94a", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cnc(Br)cc1Cl", "smiles_random": "c1c(Cl)c(F)cnc1Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cnc(Br)cc1Cl\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cnc(Br)cc1Cl", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "afbecac9-f3c9-440f-b705-045b7648d8e7", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cnc(Cl)cc1Br", "smiles_random": "n1c(Cl)cc(c(c1)F)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cnc(Cl)cc1Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cnc(Cl)cc1Br", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "91705807-5079-4daf-8bb0-f6f8b024568b", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1nccc(I)c1Br", "smiles_random": "Brc1c(I)ccnc1F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1nccc(I)c1Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1nccc(I)c1Br", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "f185a5aa-1f59-4d50-8ecb-d1a293028a70", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1ncc(Br)cc1I", "smiles_random": "c1c(Br)cc(c(F)n1)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1ncc(Br)cc1I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1ncc(Br)cc1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "382c6565-3bf8-4c8c-8127-10adf37fa40c", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1ncc(I)cc1Br", "smiles_random": "Brc1cc(cnc1F)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1ncc(I)cc1Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1ncc(I)cc1Br", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "79c86cc5-6b3a-45bb-9c0e-82cd443bc730", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cc(Br)c(I)cn1", "smiles_random": "c1(cc(c(I)cn1)Br)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cc(Br)c(I)cn1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(Br)c(I)cn1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "bc3c5a5a-caa1-4e31-9f6a-3f065de78b7b", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1nc(Br)ccc1I", "smiles_random": "Fc1c(ccc(n1)Br)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1nc(Br)ccc1I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1nc(Br)ccc1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "97892de8-a10d-4873-9970-4f0b4c50a229", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1ccc(I)nc1Cl", "smiles_random": "c1(Cl)c(F)ccc(n1)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1ccc(I)nc1Cl\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1ccc(I)nc1Cl", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "15408f46-f79d-44f2-bc2b-1a48ffc753dc", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Clc1nc(Br)ccc1I", "smiles_random": "c1(I)ccc(nc1Cl)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nClc1nc(Br)ccc1I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1nc(Br)ccc1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "6ee35d45-8cc8-4f7b-a057-d4c031f8c51c", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1ccc(I)c(Br)n1", "smiles_random": "n1c(F)ccc(c1Br)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1ccc(I)c(Br)n1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1ccc(I)c(Br)n1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "49c892e5-7e82-479d-a114-c0f5b11ebe91", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cc(I)c(Br)cn1", "smiles_random": "c1c(c(I)cc(n1)F)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cc(I)c(Br)cn1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(I)c(Br)cn1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "46191137-92ab-4117-a4a2-9155e89dcbdb", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Clc1cc(Br)ncc1I", "smiles_random": "Brc1cc(Cl)c(cn1)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nClc1cc(Br)ncc1I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1cc(Br)ncc1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "e9144e4c-72f4-4f8b-8b5d-75b2c3903014", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cnc(I)c(Br)c1", "smiles_random": "Brc1c(ncc(F)c1)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cnc(I)c(Br)c1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cnc(I)c(Br)c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "eb0c454f-8510-47af-979c-de10d59982e1", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cc(Cl)ncc1I", "smiles_random": "c1c(ncc(c1F)I)Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cc(Cl)ncc1I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(Cl)ncc1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "d8ebc40f-aa80-406c-bb86-59dc962a12ef", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cncc(Cl)c1I", "smiles_random": "c1c(c(I)c(cn1)F)Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cncc(Cl)c1I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cncc(Cl)c1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "a273ae19-1761-4948-90b5-72547048b99e", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cc(Cl)cc(Br)n1", "smiles_random": "c1c(nc(Br)cc1Cl)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cc(Cl)cc(Br)n1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(Cl)cc(Br)n1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "65725327-0693-49d2-8516-6efe62bf10df", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cnc(Cl)cc1I", "smiles_random": "c1c(Cl)ncc(F)c1I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cnc(Cl)cc1I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cnc(Cl)cc1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "806b5057-d0ac-456a-88c0-3b0b76a81cd6", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1cc(Br)ncc1Cl", "smiles_random": "Brc1cc(c(cn1)Cl)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cc(Br)ncc1Cl\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(Br)ncc1Cl", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "f1453fd9-7e16-4346-99c7-a3f7d6d7bf25", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Pyridine_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Pyridine", "scaffold_smiles": "n1ccccc1", "smiles": "Fc1nccc(Br)c1I", "smiles_random": "c1(c(F)nccc1Br)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1nccc(Br)c1I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1nccc(Br)c1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "326415c3-8f41-4d31-ab92-2d25400d2ecd", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Fc1c(Br)noc1I", "smiles_random": "Fc1c(onc1Br)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1c(Br)noc1I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1c(Br)noc1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "5c68ebca-602c-4e80-aea7-4b4c388f7495", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Fc1onc(Br)c1Cl", "smiles_random": "c1(Cl)c(onc1Br)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1onc(Br)c1Cl\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1onc(Br)c1Cl", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "ec40ca79-4805-4d4a-91be-de272d3d2fd5", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Fc1noc(Cl)c1I", "smiles_random": "c1(Cl)onc(F)c1I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1noc(Cl)c1I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1noc(Cl)c1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "dd6b8d2d-44c5-4786-b9d1-f96746df86ff", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Fc1c(Br)noc1Cl", "smiles_random": "Brc1noc(Cl)c1F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1c(Br)noc1Cl\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1c(Br)noc1Cl", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "e8ae21a3-b17d-4074-b07e-8a9884998d16", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Fc1c(Br)noc1I", "smiles_random": "n1c(c(c(I)o1)F)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1c(Br)noc1I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1c(Br)noc1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "d978507b-0b4b-4187-9a8a-9c7039710685", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Fc1c(I)noc1Cl", "smiles_random": "c1(F)c(onc1I)Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1c(I)noc1Cl\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1c(I)noc1Cl", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "b46844b8-de38-4a45-bc7d-e38a9dd80488", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Fc1onc(I)c1Br", "smiles_random": "n1c(c(c(o1)F)Br)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1onc(I)c1Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1onc(I)c1Br", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "f9cba3d8-1d08-42a7-ac61-169e1d04f22e", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Clc1onc(I)c1Br", "smiles_random": "Brc1c(onc1I)Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nClc1onc(I)c1Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1onc(I)c1Br", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "e639b2dd-3d55-45e0-853e-83fbbbf2828a", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Fc1noc(Cl)c1I", "smiles_random": "Clc1c(I)c(no1)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1noc(Cl)c1I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1noc(Cl)c1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "36ddb393-a621-4c5f-bd2b-cb23f631e303", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Clc1noc(I)c1Br", "smiles_random": "o1c(c(c(n1)Cl)Br)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nClc1noc(I)c1Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1noc(I)c1Br", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "63c13f2f-a4ae-4590-8d63-4751954bb8ec", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Fc1noc(I)c1Br", "smiles_random": "o1nc(c(Br)c1I)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1noc(I)c1Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1noc(I)c1Br", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "08cd4c8d-6f15-4eba-9400-4e4723464def", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Fc1noc(Br)c1I", "smiles_random": "n1c(c(I)c(o1)Br)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1noc(Br)c1I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1noc(Br)c1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "b5cc0241-9382-4c97-bee7-f53ff30689f0", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Fc1onc(I)c1Cl", "smiles_random": "Ic1c(Cl)c(on1)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1onc(I)c1Cl\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1onc(I)c1Cl", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "08b64969-f5eb-4ad9-98d5-22975a404d91", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Fc1c(Br)noc1Cl", "smiles_random": "n1c(Br)c(c(Cl)o1)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1c(Br)noc1Cl\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1c(Br)noc1Cl", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "863b4a05-de6a-4d7b-a6d7-514e6f4780f3", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Fc1noc(Br)c1I", "smiles_random": "n1oc(Br)c(c1F)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1noc(Br)c1I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1noc(Br)c1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "bff8d3eb-755b-4cf5-aaea-923b5abaa3a3", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Fc1noc(Br)c1I", "smiles_random": "Ic1c(noc1Br)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1noc(Br)c1I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1noc(Br)c1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "9ce604b9-afac-4044-a5e0-3653b81007e5", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Fc1onc(Cl)c1Br", "smiles_random": "c1(Cl)noc(c1Br)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1onc(Cl)c1Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1onc(Cl)c1Br", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "841a9c4f-0db3-4c74-bbf0-40a4f68d980c", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Clc1noc(Br)c1I", "smiles_random": "n1oc(Br)c(I)c1Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nClc1noc(Br)c1I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1noc(Br)c1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "bc7b0953-edc1-4d28-9c63-997a434706bf", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Clc1noc(Br)c1I", "smiles_random": "Clc1c(I)c(on1)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nClc1noc(Br)c1I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1noc(Br)c1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "4dc4b441-9b96-4670-aa13-1118e23b2fba", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Isoxazole_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Isoxazole", "scaffold_smiles": "o1nccc1", "smiles": "Fc1c(Br)noc1I", "smiles_random": "c1(c(c(Br)no1)F)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1c(Br)noc1I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1c(Br)noc1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "ef6639f9-7376-49c4-b17e-27e2be2577e0", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Fc1cccc2c(Br)cc(I)cc12", "smiles_random": "c12c(c(F)ccc1)cc(I)cc2Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cccc2c(Br)cc(I)cc12\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cccc2c(Br)cc(I)cc12", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "6ff1ce2b-cb60-4c81-9c22-c5cb8c469777", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Fc1cc(I)cc2c(Cl)cccc12", "smiles_random": "c1c2c(cc(cc2F)I)c(Cl)cc1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cc(I)cc2c(Cl)cccc12\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(I)cc2c(Cl)cccc12", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "b40b11a9-5455-4021-be97-958dca8fabbf", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Fc1ccc2c(I)cccc2c1Cl", "smiles_random": "c1c2c(c(F)ccc2c(cc1)I)Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1ccc2c(I)cccc2c1Cl\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1ccc2c(I)cccc2c1Cl", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "6fcb7ba3-cf2a-4e6e-afa3-61c9d0c5e3b7", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Fc1cc(Br)c(Cl)c2ccccc12", "smiles_random": "c12c(c(F)cc(c2Cl)Br)cccc1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cc(Br)c(Cl)c2ccccc12\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(Br)c(Cl)c2ccccc12", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "18e424dc-2c2a-4cfa-a861-268a774c5c93", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Clc1cc(I)cc2c(Br)cccc12", "smiles_random": "c1(cc2c(cccc2Br)c(c1)Cl)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nClc1cc(I)cc2c(Br)cccc12\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1cc(I)cc2c(Br)cccc12", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "6b79f82c-2bf6-4052-bb11-67c3a2ff50ba", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Clc1c(I)ccc2cc(Br)ccc12", "smiles_random": "Clc1c2ccc(cc2ccc1I)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nClc1c(I)ccc2cc(Br)ccc12\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1c(I)ccc2cc(Br)ccc12", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "f6b5fc37-6bed-4b3a-9b94-93040895e580", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Fc1cccc2c(Br)c(I)ccc12", "smiles_random": "Fc1c2ccc(I)c(Br)c2ccc1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cccc2c(Br)c(I)ccc12\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cccc2c(Br)c(I)ccc12", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "1c8c14da-9acf-4cc1-9d55-4ea5206c9743", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Clc1c(Br)cc(I)c2ccccc12", "smiles_random": "Ic1cc(c(c2ccccc12)Cl)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nClc1c(Br)cc(I)c2ccccc12\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1c(Br)cc(I)c2ccccc12", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "6263d101-a50e-4b51-a7ef-bf05420385d1", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Fc1cc(Br)c2cc(Cl)ccc2c1", "smiles_random": "c1c(F)cc(Br)c2c1ccc(Cl)c2"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cc(Br)c2cc(Cl)ccc2c1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(Br)c2cc(Cl)ccc2c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "8082ed36-e001-4947-be72-dbab016033f9", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Clc1cccc2ccc(Br)c(I)c12", "smiles_random": "c12ccc(c(c2c(Cl)ccc1)I)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nClc1cccc2ccc(Br)c(I)c12\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1cccc2ccc(Br)c(I)c12", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "9bf3a9c2-8496-45d1-8544-ea34b62ee62b", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Fc1cc(I)c2cc(Cl)ccc2c1", "smiles_random": "Ic1cc(F)cc2ccc(cc12)Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cc(I)c2cc(Cl)ccc2c1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(I)c2cc(Cl)ccc2c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "68a4b1f3-cfe9-4ac7-8cea-5a9414b19a52", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Fc1cc(I)c2c(Br)cccc2c1", "smiles_random": "c1ccc(Br)c2c1cc(F)cc2I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cc(I)c2c(Br)cccc2c1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(I)c2c(Br)cccc2c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "f5c7db09-6524-4896-bf7f-3a2b64c98b6f", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Fc1cc2ccc(Cl)cc2cc1I", "smiles_random": "c1c(c(cc2cc(ccc12)Cl)I)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cc2ccc(Cl)cc2cc1I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc2ccc(Cl)cc2cc1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "fb972162-3757-44c7-8a99-ec8be2d554f8", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Fc1cccc2cc(I)cc(Cl)c12", "smiles_random": "c1c(Cl)c2c(cc1I)cccc2F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cccc2cc(I)cc(Cl)c12\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cccc2cc(I)cc(Cl)c12", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "06d4a0df-7c8a-42d3-ac51-1930cf07c9ed", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Fc1cccc2ccc(I)c(Cl)c12", "smiles_random": "c1cc2c(c(Cl)c1I)c(ccc2)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cccc2ccc(I)c(Cl)c12\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cccc2ccc(I)c(Cl)c12", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "a19522d7-f8c4-4328-83ea-c888a8899460", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Fc1cc2cccc(I)c2cc1Br", "smiles_random": "c1(c(cc2c(c1)c(I)ccc2)F)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cc2cccc(I)c2cc1Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc2cccc(I)c2cc1Br", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "6f02f661-9fdc-4e04-b164-91104366ccda", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Fc1cc(I)c2cc(Br)ccc2c1", "smiles_random": "c1(ccc2c(c1)c(cc(c2)F)I)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cc(I)c2cc(Br)ccc2c1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(I)c2cc(Br)ccc2c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "179c72a0-b1a4-406e-85f4-9339e21b063d", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Clc1cc(I)c2ccc(Br)cc2c1", "smiles_random": "c1(Cl)cc2c(c(I)c1)ccc(Br)c2"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nClc1cc(I)c2ccc(Br)cc2c1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1cc(I)c2ccc(Br)cc2c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "8ca5db5a-ef0a-475c-a578-c7b3b96a347a", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Clc1ccc2cc(Br)c(I)cc2c1", "smiles_random": "c1c(Cl)cc2c(c1)cc(c(I)c2)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nClc1ccc2cc(Br)c(I)cc2c1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1ccc2cc(Br)c(I)cc2c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "4b77a0e9-adbf-4df4-82bf-6980c9800edb", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Napthalene_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Napthalene", "scaffold_smiles": "c12ccccc1cccc2", "smiles": "Clc1ccc2cccc(I)c2c1Br", "smiles_random": "Ic1cccc2ccc(Cl)c(Br)c21"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nClc1ccc2cccc(I)c2c1Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1ccc2cccc(I)c2c1Br", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "827e2317-78f2-46c6-8e15-88a1fc2571f5", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Clc1nc2cc(I)ccc2cc1Br", "smiles_random": "c12c(cc(cc1)I)nc(c(c2)Br)Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nClc1nc2cc(I)ccc2cc1Br\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1nc2cc(I)ccc2cc1Br", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "41dd4f30-29c8-43e2-8ac9-912c15c7c6c0", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Fc1ccnc2c(I)c(Cl)ccc12", "smiles_random": "c1nc2c(c(F)c1)ccc(Cl)c2I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1ccnc2c(I)c(Cl)ccc12\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1ccnc2c(I)c(Cl)ccc12", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "98fb8594-a7d4-4071-a41a-b0651d077429", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Clc1ccc2c(Br)ccnc2c1I", "smiles_random": "c1c2c(ccnc2c(I)c(c1)Cl)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nClc1ccc2c(Br)ccnc2c1I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1ccc2c(Br)ccnc2c1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "d9e01abf-ae43-4c1f-a94e-aa72d7695a66", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Fc1cnc2ccc(Cl)c(I)c2c1", "smiles_random": "c1c(F)cnc2ccc(c(c12)I)Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cnc2ccc(Cl)c(I)c2c1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cnc2ccc(Cl)c(I)c2c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "fa4eebab-81d3-4e1e-816c-70fa741fa7f8", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Fc1ccc2ncc(I)c(Br)c2c1", "smiles_random": "c1c(ccc2c1c(Br)c(cn2)I)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1ccc2ncc(I)c(Br)c2c1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1ccc2ncc(I)c(Br)c2c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "871afbca-d49e-4c49-9e05-7d3cad35e470", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Fc1cccc2nc(I)cc(Cl)c12", "smiles_random": "c1ccc(c2c1nc(cc2Cl)I)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cccc2nc(I)cc(Cl)c12\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cccc2nc(I)cc(Cl)c12", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "2cd5d810-cc62-445a-bde7-bc6dca570f3c", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Fc1cc2cccnc2c(I)c1Cl", "smiles_random": "Fc1c(Cl)c(c2c(c1)cccn2)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cc2cccnc2c(I)c1Cl\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc2cccnc2c(I)c1Cl", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "edd2a4f7-c421-421c-b39c-ed28cd0f77ec", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Fc1cccc2nc(Br)cc(Cl)c12", "smiles_random": "Clc1cc(nc2c1c(F)ccc2)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cccc2nc(Br)cc(Cl)c12\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cccc2nc(Br)cc(Cl)c12", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "f896ea60-f9f1-42cb-8a8a-b0cd69640ea3", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Fc1cc(Cl)c2nc(Br)ccc2c1", "smiles_random": "n1c2c(cc(cc2Cl)F)ccc1Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cc(Cl)c2nc(Br)ccc2c1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(Cl)c2nc(Br)ccc2c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "63da53ee-da24-4fa6-821d-43ad843bc349", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Fc1c(Br)cnc2c(I)cccc12", "smiles_random": "c1nc2c(cccc2c(F)c1Br)I"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1c(Br)cnc2c(I)cccc12\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1c(Br)cnc2c(I)cccc12", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "4932bf4b-d799-4464-a332-2a2479d3668c", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Fc1cc2c(Br)cccc2nc1I", "smiles_random": "Brc1cccc2c1cc(F)c(I)n2"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cc2c(Br)cccc2nc1I\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc2c(Br)cccc2nc1I", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "f940e9d5-8387-4a09-aaef-7c8c61f8bc5c", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Clc1cc(Br)cc2ncc(I)cc12", "smiles_random": "c1c(cc(c2cc(I)cnc12)Cl)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nClc1cc(Br)cc2ncc(I)cc12\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1cc(Br)cc2ncc(I)cc12", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "aca0d4ec-ade1-4ea5-87f1-98d28948f1f2", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Clc1ccc2ccc(I)c(Br)c2n1", "smiles_random": "Ic1ccc2ccc(Cl)nc2c1Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nClc1ccc2ccc(I)c(Br)c2n1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1ccc2ccc(I)c(Br)c2n1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "a2fb4355-532e-4fac-a5b7-a1992d819463", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Fc1ccc2c(Br)c(I)ccc2n1", "smiles_random": "c12c(c(Br)c(I)cc1)ccc(n2)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1ccc2c(Br)c(I)ccc2n1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1ccc2c(Br)c(I)ccc2n1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "f02635a0-42b1-47f3-95da-71ba0f2509cd", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Clc1ccnc2cc(I)cc(Br)c12", "smiles_random": "c1(Br)c2c(ccnc2cc(c1)I)Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nClc1ccnc2cc(I)cc(Br)c12\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1ccnc2cc(I)cc(Br)c12", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "4142878d-5f85-4773-9e7d-c5ba6a464f27", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Fc1cc(Cl)c2cc(I)ccc2n1", "smiles_random": "c12nc(F)cc(c1cc(cc2)I)Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cc(Cl)c2cc(I)ccc2n1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cc(Cl)c2cc(I)ccc2n1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "1736594e-0ed1-45de-8166-0206eda00c37", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Fc1ccc2nc(Br)ccc2c1Cl", "smiles_random": "Fc1ccc2c(c1Cl)ccc(n2)Br"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1ccc2nc(Br)ccc2c1Cl\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1ccc2nc(Br)ccc2c1Cl", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "7143979a-1cc1-4acd-ba1e-3a172af0ad67", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Clc1cc(Br)c2cccc(I)c2n1", "smiles_random": "c1(cc(Br)c2c(n1)c(I)ccc2)Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nClc1cc(Br)c2cccc(I)c2n1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1cc(Br)c2cccc(I)c2n1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "744c2b97-71b6-4c57-a18c-6c7ba87ea0a0", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Fc1cccc2c(Br)cc(I)nc12", "smiles_random": "c1cc(c2c(c(cc(I)n2)Br)c1)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1cccc2c(Br)cc(I)nc12\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1cccc2c(Br)cc(I)nc12", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
{"uuid": "d0a317e8-ed91-4bb7-a4e4-6819d16c80c9", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "Quinoline_canonical", "meta_data": {"scaffold": "Quinoline", "scaffold_smiles": "C1=CC=C2C(=C1)C=CC=N2", "smiles": "Fc1nc2ccccc2c(Br)c1Cl", "smiles_random": "c1ccc2c(Br)c(Cl)c(F)nc2c1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFc1nc2ccccc2c(Br)c1Cl\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Fc1nc2ccccc2c(Br)c1Cl", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": false}
